var myQuestions = [
	{
		question: "What is the range of byte data type in Java?",
		answers: {
			a: '-128 to 127',
			b: '-32768 to 32767',
			c: '-2147483648 to 2147483647',
                        d: 'None of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: "Which one is a valid declaration of a boolean? ",
		answers: {
			a: 'boolean b1 = 1;',
			b: 'boolean b2 = "false";',
			c: 'boolean b3 = false;',
                        d: 'boolean b4 = "true";'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
{
		question: "What will be the output of the following Java code? <br>class asciicodes <br>{<br>public static void main(String args[]) {<br> char var1 = 'A';<br> char var2 = 'a';<br>System.out.println((int)var1 + " +" "+ "+ (int)var2);<br>}<br> }",
		answers: {
			a: '162',
			b: '65 97',
			c: '67 95',
                        d: '66 98'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Which of these is an incorrect array declaration? ",
		answers: {
			a: 'int arr[] = new int[5]',
			b: 'int [] arr = new int[5]',
			c: 'int arr[] = new int[5]',
                        d: 'int arr[] = int [5] new'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "Which of these is an incorrect Statement?",
		answers: {
			a: 'It is necessary to use new operator to initialize an array',
			b: 'Array can be initialized using comma separated expressions surrounded by curly braces',
			c: 'Array can be initialized when they are declared',
                        d: 'None of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "What is the output of relational operators?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Integer',
			b: 'Boolean',
			c: 'Characters',
                        d: 'Double'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "What will be the output of the following Java code? <br>class Relational_operator<br>{<br>public static void main(String args[])<br>{<br>int var1 = 5; <br>int var2 = 6;<br>System.out.print(var1 > var2);<br>} <br>}",
		answers: {
			a: '1',
			b: '0',
			c: 'true',
                        d: 'false'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "When does method overloading is determined?",
		answers: {
			a: 'At run time',
			b: 'At compile time',
			c: 'At coding time',
                        d: 'At execution time'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Which of the following is a valid declaration of an object of class Box?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Box obj = new Box();',
			b: 'Box obj = new Box;',
			c: 'obj = new Box();',
                        d: 'new Box obj;'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: " Which of these statement is incorrect?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Every class must contain a main() method',
			b: 'Applets do not require a main() method at all',
			c: 'There can be only one main() method in a program',
                        d: 'main() method must be made public'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	}
];